http://www.4electronicwarehouse.com/policies/privacy-policy

Free Ground Shipping On All Orders.
Free Ground Shipping On All Orders.
GPS Devices
Questions?
Privacy policy
Your Electronic Warehouse has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website:
Our site uses information request forms for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their name & email address). Contact information from the request forms is used to send orders and information about our products to our customers. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
Your Electronic Warehouse does not rent or sell your personal information to third parties.
We may need to share your personal information with certain third parties such as our service providers and other representatives acting on our behalf for limited purposes. For example, we may share personal information with third parties to perform services on our behalf such as:
Fulfilling our customers' orders
Sending Your Electronic Warehouse marketing communications
Sending regular mail and e-mail on behalf of Your Electronic Warehouse
Processing credit card payments
The third parties with whom we conduct business are only authorized to use your information to perform the service for which they were hired. As part of our agreement with them, they are required to follow the privacy guidelines we provide them and to take reasonable measures to ensure your personal information is secure.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
Copyright © 2020 Your Electronic Warehouse.
Added to your cart:
Subtotal
